overnightprints.com 2019-03-02

# Business Cards | Postcards | Brochures | Online Printing

Overnight Prints is committed to protecting your information, how it's used and how it's shared, and we appreciate you choosing to do business with us. This page describes our privacy policy. By visiting Overnight Prints, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. 

### Personal Information About Customers Gathered By Overnight Prints

The information we learn from customers helps us personalize and continually improve your shopping experience at Overnight Prints. 

Here are the types of information we gather:

  * **Information You Give Us:** We receive and store any information you enter on our Web site or give us in any other way. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future shopping for you, improving our business, and communicating with you. 

  * **Automatic Information:** We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many Web sites, we use "cookies," and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses Overnight Prints. 

  * **E-mail Communications:** To help us make e-mails more useful and interesting, we often receive a confirmation when you open e-mail from Overnight Prints if your computer supports such capabilities. If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please follow the unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of any e-mail message you receive from Overnight Prints. 

  * **Information From Other Sources:** We might receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information. 

### Cookies

  * Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide certain features and improve our business. 

  * The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. Additionally, you can disable or delete similar data used by browser add-ons, such as Flash cookies, by changing the add-on's settings or visiting the website of its manufacturer. However, because cookies allow you to take advantage of some of Overnight Prints's essential features, we recommend that you leave them turned on. For instance, if you block or otherwise reject our cookies, you will not be able to add items to your Shopping Cart, proceed to Checkout, or to Sign in to Overnight Prints's website. 

### How Do We Use Your Information

  * We may use your information in a number of ways, including the following: 

  * In order to serve you better, we may combine the information you provide us online, in our stores and through our catalogs. We use that information to improve your overall shopping experience. 

  * To improve the content on our website. For example, we may use cookies to find out which parts of our site or our products are visited most often. To enhance your online shopping experience. For example, we may use it to recognize you and welcome you to the site. 

  * For marketing and promotional purposes. For example, we send out email and direct mail to our online and store customers about products or events that we think may be of interest to them. We also may send you offers for discounts or free services (e.g., free gift wrap or shipping) on our site or in our stores. For customer service purposes, such as contacting customers who have not checked out to follow up on abandoned shopping carts or to see if there was a problem with their use of the site. 

### Information Sharing

Information about our customers is an important part of our business, and we are not in the business of selling it to others. We share customer information only with reputable corporate partners. 

  * **Third-Party Service Providers:** We may employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include but are not limited to, fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, providing search results and links (including paid listings and links), processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions. 

  * **Business Transfers:** As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy other companies, subsidiaries, or business units. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets. Also, in the unlikely event that Overnight Prints, or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information will of course be one of the transferred assets. 

  * **Protection Of Overnight Prints And Others:** We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce or apply our Terms of Service and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Overnight Prints, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. 

### Information Security

  * We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input. 

  * We reveal only the last five digits of your credit card numbers when confirming an order. Of course, we transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing. 

### Third-Party Advertisers And Links to Other Websites

Our site includes third-party advertising and links to other websites. These third-party websites and advertisers, or Internet advertising companies working on their behalf, sometimes use technology to send (or "serve") the advertisements that appear on our website directly to your browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use cookies, JavaScript, web beacons (also known as action tags or single-pixel gifs), and other technologies to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. We do not have access to or control over cookies or other features that they may use, and the information practices of these advertisers and third-party websites are not covered by this Privacy Policy. Please contact them directly for more information about their privacy practices. 

### Process to Review and Make Changes to Personal Information

  * As discussed above, you can always choose not to provide information, even though it might be needed to make a purchase or to take advantage other Overnight Prints products and features. 

  * The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. Additionally, you can disable or delete similar data used by browser add-ons, such as Flash cookies, by changing the add-on's settings or visiting the Website of its manufacturer. However, because cookies allow you to take advantage of some of Overnight Prints's essential features, we recommend that you leave them turned on. For instance, if you block or otherwise reject our cookies, you may not be able to add items to your Shopping Cart, proceed to Checkout, or use any Overnight Prints's products and services that require you to sign in. 

### Children's Use of Overnight Prints Website

Overnight Prints does not sell products for purchase by children. Any children's products we may sell are for purchase by adults. Children may only use our website with consent from their guardian. 

### Terms Of Service, Notices, And Revisions

If you choose to visit Overnight Prints, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Policy and our Terms of Service, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the state of California. 

Our business changes constantly, and our Privacy Policy and the Terms of Service will change also. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, but you should check our Web site frequently to see recent changes. It is your responsibility to review this document periodically for changes. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account. 

### Information You Give Us

You provide such information when you search, buy, post, participate in a contest or questionnaire, or communicate with customer service. For example, you provide information when you search for a product; place an order with Overnight Prints or one of our third-party sellers; provide information by filling out a form; communicate with us by phone, e-mail, or otherwise; complete a questionnaire or a contest entry form; provide reviews. As a result of those actions, you might supply us with such information as your name, address, and phone numbers; credit card information; people to whom purchases have been shipped, including addresses and phone number; e-mail addresses. 

### Automatic Information

Examples of the information we collect and analyze include the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet; login; e-mail address; password; computer and connection information such as browser type, version, and time zone setting, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system, and platform; purchase history; the full Uniform Resource Locator (URL) clickstream to, through, and from our Website, including date and time; cookie number; products you viewed or searched for; and the phone number you used to call our toll free number. We may also use browser data such as cookies, Flash cookies (also known as Flash Local Shared Objects), or similar data on certain parts of our Website for fraud prevention and other purposes. During some visits we may use software tools such as JavaScript to measure and collect session information, including page response times, tools such as JavaScript to measure and collect session information, including page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), and methods used to browse away from the page. 

### Information From Other Sources

Examples of information we receive from other sources include updated delivery and address information from our carriers or other third parties, which we use to correct our records and deliver your next purchase or communication more easily; account information, purchase or redemption information, and page-view information from some merchants with which we operate co-branded businesses or for which we provide technical, fulfillment, advertising, or other services; search term and search result information from some searches conducted through the Web search features offered by our subsidiaries; search results and links, including paid listings (such as Sponsored Links). 

If any questions or disputes of this Privacy Policy arise, please contact Overnight Prints at [service@overnightprints.com](mailto:service@overnightprints.com), and we will do our best to answer or resolve your issue. You may also choose to contact us at: 

**Overnight Prints  
7582 Las Vegas Blvd. S. Suite #487, Las Vegas, NV, 89123**
